Okay, the Steelers game is almost on.
Time to fire up Steel City Game Day.
Let’s check the Wire.
I’m feeling good about this season.
Okay, time to get the pregame picks in.
I wonder who’s going to get the crown today.
Seems like Alex is always lucky
with these kinds of things.
Okay, Flash Picks are up. Who are you picking?
I don’t know. The Falcons defense looks pretty tough.
I’m not sure the Steelers are going to score
before halftime here.
Dang, it’s close to the end of the game.
Who’s going to have the most points in our crew?
It better not be Alex.
She always wins.
Oh man, Alex took it.
Alex took it. I knew it.
Oh yes, took the crown for this game.
I have a feeling I’m going to take it for the season.
Oh well, at least we have a Steeler victory.
Here we go, Steelers!